{
    "subject": "resource/Shahid_(film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Tigmanshu_Dhulia",
    "human_readable": "Shahid film stars Tigmanshu Dhulia.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9214590191841125,
            "question": "Besides directing, what other role did Tigmanshu Dhulia have in Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8876898884773254,
            "question": "Which film features Tigmanshu Dhulia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8239613771438599,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Tigmanshu Dhulia."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8101499676704407,
            "question": "Who stars in the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.796799898147583,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie that Tigmanshu Dhulia acted in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7714837789535522,
            "question": "Is Tigmanshu Dhulia an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7266280055046082,
            "question": "Who directed the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6713528037071228,
            "question": "What is the name of the actor who starred in the film Shahid?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6457064747810364,
            "question": "Has Tigmanshu Dhulia ever been an actor in a film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.507146418094635,
            "question": "What is the genre of the film Shahid?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Shahid film stars Tigmanshu Dhulia.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2645_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Tigmanshu Dhulia ever been an actor in a film?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2645_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the actor who starred in the film Shahid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2645_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who directed the film Shahid?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2645_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_118.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_125.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_130.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2645_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in the requested format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2645/re-ranker-msmarco/130.txt states that Tigmanshu Dhulia will be seen in Hansal Mehta's Shahid, and the document at file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2645/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt lists Tigmanshu Dhulia as one of the cast members in the film Shahid."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents state that Tigmanshu Dhulia will be playing a lawyer and a mentor of sorts to Rajkumar Yadav in the film \"Shahid,\" which confirms that Tigmanshu Dhulia stars in the film Shahid."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}